cableguyapp.com 2016-09-01

# Cable Guy TV Operator | Dish Billing |Mobicollector

##  Privacy Policy

Privacy of those who visit our Web sites, register for our platform and services online and security of their stored data is of utmost importance to MOBICOLLECTOR Ltd. We think it is important for you to understand when and why we collect personally identifiable information and how we may use it. This Privacy Policy describes MOBICOLLECTOR data collection and security and use policies. Please read the entire Privacy Policy before providing any personally identifiable information to us or storing any of your data on our servers.

## Notice

MOBICOLLECTOR collects personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address, and credit card information only if you provide this information to us voluntarily. Some of this information you must provide to us if you want to use our platform. The voluntary information we collect is used for internal verification to complete transactions; ensure appropriate legal use of MOBICOLLECTOR platform; provide notification to licensees about updates to MOBICOLLECTOR’s and our affiliates’ software, data, and services; and help provide technical and product support to our users. Where appropriate, MOBICOLLECTOR may pass this data to an MOBICOLLECTOR international distributor that provides the above services in your country or to an MOBICOLLECTOR affiliate whose software, data, and services provide solutions to meet your needs. Our affiliates are also committed to protecting personally identifiable information as described in their privacy statements/policies. MOBICOLLECTOR may also use your name, address, and e-mail to send you marketing materials, user conference information, and newsletters unless you notify us that you do not want to receive these materials. Occasionally, MOBICOLLECTOR uses the services of bonded mailing houses that are authorized to use your personally identifiable data only for the benefit of MOBICOLLECTOR and its affiliates. While browsing the MOBICOLLECTOR Web site, you may be able to access the Web sites of our affiliates and third parties through a hyperlink. MOBICOLLECTOR assumes no responsibility for the privacy practices of third parties’ Web sites and suggests you review the privacy statements/policies on such Web sites before sharing your personally identifiable data.

##   
Collection

Certain information, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, may be stored through the use of “cookies” intended to speed access to MOBICOLLECTOR information and services. A cookie is a small file that can be used to tell us when you visit our Web sites and track your browsing preferences. MOBICOLLECTOR does not use cookies to store information such as credit card numbers, telephone numbers, or other information you provide. To maintain your privacy, you can disable your browser’s ability to accept cookies. MOBICOLLECTOR Web sites may require registration to gain access to special services, license keys, or other features. This information will be used to provide support and deliver specialized services. MOBICOLLECTOR may also collect personally identifiable information you provide when you order and register software, data, or services; enter contests; order newsletters; register for training or conferences; or make requests that require a direct response to you.

## Choice

If you submit personal information, MOBICOLLECTOR may contact you or send you marketing information about software or services. If you do not wish to receive this information, you may notify us by sending an e-mail to info@mobicollector.com as indicated below. Keep in mind, however, that you may not receive valuable information as a result of your election to be removed from mailing lists. Other than as described in this Privacy Policy, MOBICOLLECTOR will not disclose your personally identifiable information unless required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of MOBICOLLECTOR, or (3) as part of a transfer of assets to a successor in interest. Except as stated, MOBICOLLECTOR does not rent, sell, or otherwise share personally identifiable information.

## Access

MOBICOLLECTOR will permit you to access information about you in our database by contacting us at info@mobicollecor.com. If you believe any of the information is incorrect or needs updating, please advise us. We will correct our records upon verification of the requested change. If you no longer wish to receive e-mail or postal notifications about software, services, or special promotions, please let us know by sending an e-mail to us at info@mobicollector.com and specifying that you do not want to receive these notifications. Please provide us with your exact name and address as well as a description of the publication or mail piece you received. We will use reasonable efforts to refrain from including you when sending marketing materials to MOBICOLLECTOR clients by noting your election in our database.

MOBICOLLECTOR will take reasonable and prudent precautions to ensure that your personally identifiable data is protected against unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We will use encrypted client connections with verified security protocols (SSL), etc. to protect your credit card data and other data you have stored stored in our cloud.

If you believe for any reason that MOBICOLLECTOR has not followed these principles, please contact us at info@mobicollector.com, and MOBICOLLECTOR will act promptly to investigate, correct as appropriate, and advise you of the correction. Please identify the issue as a Privacy Policy concern in your communication to MOBICOLLECTOR.
